Contact

0963893893 (Home) tangthienan9@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/tang-thienan-0691a4195 (LinkedIn) ndtang.vercel.app/ (Personal)

Top Skills

bash script
Red Hat Linux
React Native

Certifications

Amazon Web Services Cloud Practitioner

Graph Developer - Associate

Tang Thien An

Software Developer at NAB

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

I've worked for more than 2 years as a Front-end ReactJs developer and I love it. On the other hand, I have the ability to catch up with new technology quite fast.

The thing that let me work well is people, it would be wonderful if my teammate could help me develop myself in both technical and life.

Experience

NAB Innovation Centre Vietnam Software Engineer December 2021 - Present (1 year 11 months) Vietnam

For full-time official work, my team collaborated with Australian and Indian teams. My squad takes responsibility for a mini-app. My role is to implement the UI within integrate BioCatch and a11y, create resolvers on BFF, write queries or mutations with Apollo, and Spike and implement new functions, mentor new members, and present any new feature or new archive to the whole team. Take sharing section, Own some training class in office...

- Team size: 12

- Role: Fullstack-Developer

FPT Software

Software Engineer

September 2020 - December 2021 (1 year 4 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Health and Care Project

- Team size: 10

- Role: Front-end Developer

During my work, I have won the hackathon with my chatbox which increases the UX/UI and profit

Education

Greenwich University

Bachelor's degree, Information Technology \cdot (September 2018 - December 2022)